[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the word 'Їздити' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "のります"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the word 'сідати на поїзд' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "でんしゃにのります"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the word 'Робити пересадку' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "のりかえます"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the word 'Міняти' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "かえます"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the word 'приймати душ' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "シャワーをあびます"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the word 'Вступати' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "はいります"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the word 'Закінчити' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "だいがくをでます"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the word 'Звільнятися, кидати' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "やめます"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the word 'Натискати' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "おします"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the word 'Голова' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "あたま"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the word 'Волосся' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "かみ"
    },
    {
        "id": "12",
        "question": "How is the word 'Обличчя' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "かお"
    },
    {
        "id": "13",
        "question": "How is the word 'Очі' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "め"
    },
    {
        "id": "14",
        "question": "How is the word 'Вухо' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "みみ"
    }
]